Guide to the Red Lodge Canning Company Records 1922-1974
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Printed Materials, 1922-1943; Series V; 0.75 linear feet
  This series contains canning industry publications, Red Lodge Canning Company sample labels, and company promotional materials. This series also contains a folder of numerous birth certificates from Butte and Red Lodge, Montana (dating from 1922-1926).
  - Birth Certificates, 1922-1926 (Box-folder 108/4)
  - Canning Publications, 1934 (Box-folder 108/5)
  - Canning Publications, 1922-1939 and undated (Box-folder 108/6)
  - Canning Publications, 1926-1943 and undated (Box-folder 109/1)
  - Labels, undated (Box-folder 109/2)
  - Labels, undated (Box-folder 109/3)
  - Labels, undated (Box-folder 109/4)
  - Promotional Materials, undated (Box-folder 109/5)
- Photographs, 1926; Series VI; 73 items
  This series contains 37 images of Red Lodge Canning Company facilities and company-related events in Red Lodge, Montana as well as 36 images of company operations in Stevensville, Montana. These images include photographs of the 1972 Red Lodge Sweet Pea Parade, pea processing techniques, corn processing and cattle drives in the Bitterroot Valley, and a company-sponsored bowling team in Red Lodge.
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box xx, Photo number 78-0303)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box xx, Photo number 78-0304)
  - Employee Group Photo, Red Lodge, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):1)
  - Employee Group Photo, Red Lodge, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):2)
  - Company Machinery, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):3)
  - Future Farmers of America Exhibit, Red Lodge, Montana, 1961 (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):4)
  - Company Production Line, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):5)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1937 (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):6)
  - Billings Brewing Company Truck, Red Lodge, Montana, 1951 (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):7)
  - Billings Brewing Company Truck, Red Lodge, Montana, 1951 (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):8)
  - Red Lodge Canning Company, Harold Godfrey and M. H. Mann, undated (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):9)
  - Red Lodge Canning Company, Director, undated (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):10)
  - Red Lodge Canning Company, unidentified man, undated (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):11)
  - Company Machinery, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/3, Photo number 101(VI):12)
  - Sweet Pea Parade, Red Lodge, Montana, 1972 (Box-folder 114/4, Photo number 101(VI):13)
  - Sweet Pea Parade, Red Lodge, Montana, 1972 (Box-folder 114/4, Photo number 101(VI):14)
  - Sweet Pea Parade, Red Lodge, Montana, 1972 (Box-folder 114/4, Photo number 101(VI):15)
  - Sweet Pea Parade, Red Lodge, Montana, 1972 (Box-folder 114/4, Photo number 101(VI):16)
  - Sweet Pea Parade, Red Lodge, Montana, 1972 (Box-folder 114/4, Photo number 101(VI):17)
  - Sweet Pea Parade, Red Lodge, Montana, 1972 (Box-folder 114/4, Photo number 101(VI):18)
  - Sweet Pea Parade, Red Lodge, Montana, 1972 (Box-folder 114/4, Photo number 101(VI):19)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):20)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):21)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):22)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):23)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):24)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):25)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):26)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):27)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):28)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):29)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):30)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):31)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):32)
  - Company Building, Red Lodge, Montana, 1926 (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):33)
  - Company Machinery, Red Lodge, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):34)
  - Company Machinery, Red Lodge, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/5, Photo number 101(VI):35)
  - C. H. Aiman's Alaska Seed Pea Field, St. Anthony, Idaho, 1931 (Box-folder 114/6, Photo number 101(VI):36)
  - C. H. Aiman's Alaska Seed Pea Field, St. Anthony, Idaho, 1931 (Box-folder 114/6, Photo number 101(VI):37)
  - C. H. Aiman's Alaska Seed Pea Field, St. Anthony, Idaho, 1931 (Box-folder 114/6, Photo number 101(VI):38)
  - C. H. Aiman's Alaska Seed Pea Field, St. Anthony, Idaho, 1931 (Box-folder 114/6, Photo number 101(VI):39)
  - Stock Alaska Seed Peas, undated (Box-folder 114/6, Photo number 101(VI):40)
  - Stock Alaska Seed Peas, undated (Box-folder 114/6, Photo number 101(VI):41)
  - Red Lodge Peas and Carrots, Montana Products Bowling League, undated (Box-folder 114/6, Photo number 101(VI):42)
  - Red Lodge Peas and Carrots, Montana Products Bowling League, undated (Box-folder 114/6, Photo number 101(VI):43)
  - Red Lodge Peas and Carrots, Montana Products Bowling League, undated (Box-folder 114/6, Photo number 101(VI):44)
  - Company Building, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/7, Photo number 101(VI):45)
  - Assembly line, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/7, Photo number 101(VI):46)
  - Two unidentified men in front of tool shed, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/7, Photo number 101(VI):47)
  - Cattle drive, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/7, Photo number 101(VI):48)
  - Corn processing, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/7, Photo number 101(VI):49)
  - Assembly line, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/7, Photo number 101(VI):50)
  - Jim Measem and Jock Prichart in corn field, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/7, Photo number 101(VI):51)
  - Jim Measem and Jock Prichart in corn field, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/7, Photo number 101(VI):52)
  - "Kraut House", Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/7, Photo number 101(VI):53)
  - Corn huskers, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/7, Photo number 101(VI):54)
  - Corn processing, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/7, Photo number 101(VI):55)
  - Corn huskers, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):56)
  - Assembly line, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):57)
  - Assembly line, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):58)
  - Assembly line, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):59)
  - Assembly line, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):60)
  - Corn field, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):61)
  - Jim Measem and Jock Prichart in corn field, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):62)
  - St. Mary's Church, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):63)
  - "Mainstreet", Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):64)
  - Cattle drive, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):65)
  - Ravalli Canning Company Building, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):66)
  - Ravalli Canning Company Building, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):67)
  - Installing pipe system, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):68)
  - Company Building, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):69)
  - Company Building, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):70)
  - Company Building and two unidentified men, Stevensville, Montana, undated (Box-folder 114/8, Photo number 101(VI):71)
- Beer Distributorship, 1950-1958; Series VII; 2.25 linear feet
  This series contains correspondence and account statements for the Red Lodge Canning Company's beer distribution division, sometimes identified as the Rocky Mountain Distributing Company. This operation held beer distribution contracts with several brewing companies, local and national, for Carbon and Stillwater counties in Montana.
  - General Correspondence, 1950-1958; Subseries 1; 1.0 linear feet
    - A-Z, 1950 (Box-folder 110/1)
    - Billings Brewing Company, 1951 (Box-folder 110/2)
    - Blatz Brewing Company, 1951 (Box-folder 110/3)
    - Brewing Corporation of America, 1951 (Box-folder 110/4)
    - A-Z, 1951 (Box-folder 110/5)
    - Billings Brewing Company, 1952 (Box-folder 110/6)
    - Blatz Brewing Company, 1952 (Box-folder 110/7)
    - Brewing Corporation of America, 1952 (Box-folder 110/8)
    - Butte Brewing Company, 1952 (Box-folder 110/9)
    - Canada Dry Corporation, 1952 (Box-folder 110/10)
    - A-Z, 1952 (Box-folder 110/11)
    - Canada Dry Corporation, 1953 (Box-folder 110/12)
    - Brewing Corporation of America, 1953 (Box-folder 110/13)
    - Butte Brewing Company, 1953 (Box-folder 110/14)
    - A-Z, 1953 (Box-folder 110/15)
    - Butte Brewing Company, 1954 (Box-folder 110/16)
    - A-Z, 1954 (Box-folder 110/17)
    - Butte Brewing Company, 1955 (Box-folder 110/18)
    - A-Z, 1955 (Box-folder 110/19)
    - A-Z, 1956 (Box-folder 110/20)
    - A-Z, 1957 (Box-folder 110/21)
    - A-Z, 1958 (Box-folder 110/22)
  - Financial Records:, 1950-1958; Subseries 2; 1.25 linear feet
    - Statements, 1950 (Box-folder 111/1)
    - Statements, 1951 (Box-folder 111/2)
    - Statements, 1951 (Box-folder 111/3)
    - Statements, 1952 (Box-folder 111/4)
    - Statements, 1952 (Box-folder 111/5)
    - Statements, 1953 (Box-folder 112/1)
    - Statements, 1953 (Box-folder 112/2)
    - Statements, 1954 (Box-folder 112/3)
    - Statements, 1954 (Box-folder 112/4)
    - Statements, 1955 (Box-folder 112/5)
    - Statements, 1955 (Box-folder 112/6)
    - Statements, 1956 (Box-folder 113/1)
    - Statements, 1956 (Box-folder 113/2)
    - Statements, 1957 (Box-folder 113/3)
    - Statements, 1957 (Box-folder 113/4)
    - Statements, 1958 (Box-folder 113/5)
    - Distribution Prospectus and Blatz Brewery Proposed Contract, undated (Box-folder 113/6)
    - Rocky Mountain Distributing Company Statements, 1951 (Box-folder 113/7)
    - Rocky Mountain Distributing Company Statements, 1951 (Box-folder 114/1)
    - Rocky Mountain Distributing Company Statements, 1951 (Box-folder 114/2)